aerofex.com 2018-06-29

# Aerofex, Inc. Privacy Policy - Aerofex - Aerofex

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.aerofex.com and Aerofex, Inc and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Aerofex, Inc include www.aerofex.com and Aerofex. By using the Aerofex website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
Aerofex may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Aerofex’s products and services, we collect billing information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Aerofex. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Aerofex website.

Aerofex encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Aerofex so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Aerofex is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Aerofex website.

**Use of your Personal Information**  
Aerofex collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Aerofex may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Aerofex and its affiliates. Aerofex may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Aerofex does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Aerofex may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Aerofex, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Aerofex may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Aerofex, in order to determine what Aerofex services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content within Aerofex to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Aerofex will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Aerofex or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Aerofex; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Aerofex, or the public.

**Security of your Personal Information**  
Aerofex secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

**Children Under Thirteen**  
Aerofex does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**  
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Aerofex by contacting us at contact.aerofex.com

**Changes to this Statement**  
Aerofex will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Aerofex encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Aerofex is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**  
Aerofex welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Aerofex has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Aerofex at:

Aerofex, Inc  
PO Box 638  
Manhattan Beach, California 90267

Email Address: contact@aerofex.com  
_________________

Effective as of May 01, 2014
